I've succumbed to temptation yet again...
I can't believe I'm doing this...
Then I'll take it.
Huh? Hey, wait-!
The dog? A-and you look...
I'm not a dog.
And you shouldn't eat fries on a diet.
GIMME BACK MY FRIES!
Come back!
THOSE FRIES ARE MINE!
Quit slippin' through all these tight spaces!
Give me back my fries!
Leave me alone, ya greasy elf.
You're the one who swiped
my precious fries in the first place!
Huh?
A puppy...?
Now I get it.
You stole my fries 'cause you were
trying to get food for the puppy.
Laika's a pack leader.
She's gotta look out for her kin.
This one needs lots of food!
Groooowl
Damn dog...
Did she lose weight 'cause
she was feeding it her food?
Don't worry about Laika. She's strong.
Eat your fill, little one.
Here, take it!
Oh, thanks. Why the change of heart?
I dunno... I just felt like it...
No particular reason...
What's it saying?
"I can't eat this. It's got too much salt."
It's more health-conscious than we are...
Maybe we should go buy some dog food...
Plus-Sized Elf
The Affectionate Dog and the Dark Roast Plant
Well that was a disaster...
I'm missing out on delicious fries...
Today's Special
German Kaffee
"German"... Not sure how to read
that second word.
I'm pretty sure Germans eat potatoes.
Plus, a special means it's a good bargain...
The average person might not care,
but you can't fool a pro.
The Original
Café Siren
Maybe I'll get to eat some fries after all.
Welcome to Café Siren!
I appreciate your patience.
Here's your German coffee.
German... coffee?
That's right, German coffee.
You can add milk and sugar to your liking.
Coffee...
Isn't that what the human
always drinks in the mornings?
I think he said it's a type of liquid
extracted from beans...
Can they make it from potatoes, too?
It's a really dark color, but...
it does smell nice.
It's not food, but if it's made of potatoes...
Welcome to Café Siren!
Hello. I'm here to pick up
some coffee beans I ordered.
Of course! Give me just one moment.
Huh?
What a coincidence. Hey, Elfuda-
A-are you okay?!
The hell kind of a special is this?!
I'll stick to potatoes, thanks!
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf!
One disaster after the next...
I honestly don't think today
could get any worse...
What's that?
Oh, it's a rose bush Kusahanada gave me.
It's not doing so well...
How's it going?
See for yerself!
You look the same to me.
The fish are tasty this season...
If you want to lose weight,
I hear pork is a good option.
Pork?!
Oink...
Good afternoon!
Oh my! Hello there, you two.
Oh, what happened here?
It's starting to wilt, and it's got
white spots on its leaves...
Is it sick?
Goodness, the poor thing!
Do you mind if I take a closer look?
Oh, by all means! Please do.
Okay, here we go...
Um, what's she doing?
Alraune can use magic to
command plants at will.
Sour Spud      Sweet Spud
Move 'em, change 'em...
and heal 'em, of course.
It's a delicate skill unique to creatures
that share an even deeper connection
to nature than us elves.
Even the leaves look good as new!
That's incredible!
Thank you!
Not a problem.
That was quite a yawn.
Overdid it on the magic, huh?
Oh, that's no good...
I'm still on the job...
Sorry if I wore you out...
That reminds me!
Here, I'd planned on giving these to you
as my way of saying thanks.
Coffee beans?
Wow, those look high quality.
Don't they?!
Oh, I know! The rest of you
might as well try some, too!
Sure, I could go for some coffee.
Well, don't mind if I do!
Don't fall for it!
That crap is poison to us otherwordly beings!
What? Coffee is coffee.
I'm sure you'll like it better if you
add plenty of milk and sugar.
Should I fetch some boiling water?
Yes, please!
Is there anything else we'll need?
Nope, I've got it covered!
I brought all the essentials with me!
These are part of your present!
You... really thought of everything.
That's just the kind of person he is.
So Kusahanada, is this your
first time drinking coffee?
I've had it before.
But I don't remember how I felt about it...
You don't remember?
Mmm, it smells lovely!
I'll say!
Ain't nothin' on the shore quite like it.
And what a pretty color.
Like the finest mulch.
Mulch...
Must be a plant thing.
Well, time for a taste test.
Go ahead. I hope you like it.
It has a fruity and refreshing
acidity on the palate,
along with a slightly sweet finish.
It's delicious!
Glad to hear it.
Less bitter than sea snails, that's for sure.
It'd pair well with a pastry.
So yummy!
Different beans have different flavors.
It gets pretty in-depth!
And, in addition to fighting off drowsiness,
caffeine helps burn fat.
Y'see, caffeine stimulates the sympathetic
nervous system, triggering adrenaline and-
Ooooohhh
The heck is goin' on?!
Alraune absorb moisture and nutrients...
the properties of which affect the flowers
on their heads and their personalities.
So the coffee is the culprit!
What?!
A-are you okay?
Oh, totes.
Huh?
Like, why would you even ask me that?
I can't even!
I-is this a joke?
Why is she talking like that...?
OMG, I feel fantastic!
These vibes are fire!
A valley girl...?
Uh, will she go back to normal?
Probably... I'd imagine it's a temporary thing.
Look at all my friends!
Da-da-da-dun!
Oh crap!
Human! Stay back!
Let's give 'em a great big hug!
Watch out!
Aw, I don't get why you're so salty.
I just wanted to gas up my besties!
You're low-key giving me the ick.
I think you need to cool off!
Lit AF!
That was hilarious!
Does she look stronger to anyone else?
Why'd you give WATER to the PLANT LADY?!
Okey-dokey, it's my turn!
Is that...?!
Oink!
What the-?!
It's almost like she's drunk...
A-are you alright?!
HUMAN!
Gotcha!
Y'know...
you're way more adorbs up close!
Huh?
Why, I could just... eat you up!
Huh?!
H-H-HELP! SHE'S GONNA EAT ME!
Hold on, we're coming!
It's high time we saved you for once, human!
Oink-!
I swear I don't taste good!
Hm, fair point.
A little too piggish, IMO.
But I'm really not even that cute!
Relax, orc!
She didn't mean it as a compliment!
Now feel the wrath of the mermaid!
She got me hook, line, and sinker!
I've got this. Buy me some time
to charge up my magic!
On it.
I'll deal with that pesky ivy of hers.
I forgot to bring my arrows...
Seriously?!
Silly little elf, you're such a ditz!
Tee-hee, mlem!
Ugh, screw it!
Arrows or no arrows, I can make this work!
CHAAAAARGE!
ELFUDAAAAA!
What the...?!
Oink... oink...
I'm all washed up...
Are you guys alright?!
Just hang in there!
Now then...
it would seem we're alone at last.
Boy, am I starving.
Down the hatch you go!
Can't believe I let my guard down...
Wait, what about the human?!
Boo-hoo-hoo
Boo-hoo-hoo...
Sniffle, sniffle, sob...
Wahh, sob, sob, sniffle...
Boo-hoo-hoo...
The Alraune's Garden
Safe and sound...
...except for his pride.
Alternate Dimension
Keep Out
Entrance
So this is where she went...